A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
AJIN: DEMI-HUMAN
深く眠れるかい？
傷は癒せたかい？
Do you sleep well?
Did your wounds heal?
Just cos' they say the night is lonely
夜が寂しいからって
You don't have to force yourself
To love someone
無理して
誰かを愛さないで
They say I'm dreaming
夢を見る事だって
咽び泣く事だって
They say I'm sobbing
They say I tried to die without knowing
知りもしないまま
死んでみたって
上手に隠れたかい？
息は潜めたかい？
Did you manage to hide?
Did you hold your breath?
今が苦しいからって
Just cos' they say it's tough now
You don't have to force yourself to change
無理して自分を変えないで
Even a brave savage
勇敢な蛮人だって
悩める子羊だって
Even a troubled lamb
They are just wandering through life
回り道して生きているって
目立たないように
So I don't stand out
So I can put up with it
堪えられるように
So my train of thought won't stop yet
思考回路はまだ
止めないように
Tonight run away, run a way
It's unbelievable
今宵 RUN AWAY  RUN A WAY
嘘みたいだ
Someone take my hand
誰かこの手
掴んでくれよ
The tomorrow we can't see
Doesn't have to come
見えない明日は来なくていい
今はただ 眠りたい
Now I just want to sleep
IT'S SHOW TIME
There are just two days remaining until
the man who calls himself Sato...
（キャスター）
佐藤と名乗る男が予告した
犯行日まで―
...has announced
that he will stage an attack.
残すところ あと２日となりました
As you can see, there is already tight
security around Grant Pharmaceuticals.
ご覧のように
グラント製薬本社ビルには―
既に厳重な警備が敷かれています
Oh, dear, the world
is so dangerous nowadays.
（山中(やまなか)）
やだやだ
物騒な世の中になったもんだねぇ
あの… おばあちゃん
Ma'am.
Yes?
うん？
I have a favor to ask.
お願いがあるんだけど
FOX
SERVICE
We should be able to get inside
in about five minutes.
あと５分くらいで入れると思うけど
We're ready.
準備は出来てるよ
Hello! We're with Clean Fox Service.
どうも　クリーン･フォックス･
サービスです
We've come to repair the drainage pipes...
排水管の設備改修工事に
来たんすけど
（守衛）
改修工事？
Repair? Have you heard about this?
聞いてる？
No, I haven't heard anything.
（守衛）
いや 聞いてないな
（奥山）
いやぁ これ
こないだ現場でやっちゃいましてね
Oh, this? I hurt myself
on the job recently...
...but management says
we don't have anyone to spare.
そんでも 上は
“人手が足りねえから”っつって…
It's tough being at the bottom
of the ladder.
下っ端は つらいっすよ
（守衛）
ハハ お互いにね
I hear you on that.
ああ 改修工事だっけ？
- You said you're here for repairs?
- That's right.
そうっす
（守衛）
あ
Yeah, it's in the schedule.
ああ 確かにあるね
（エレベータのベル）
（高橋）
はぁ… やべぇ
Damn.
That was some great work.
（ゲン）
お前 すげぇな
No time for that. Let's hurry.
それより 急ごう
Mr. Sato, can you see?
佐藤さん 見える？
Yes, very well indeed.
ああ 視界良好だよ
Yeah, that's the northeast wall.
うん そこが北東側の壁面だよ
Can I leave the rest to you?
後は任せて大丈夫かい？
No problem.
問題ないよ
Which is the final point
（戸崎）
以上が亜人管理委員会からの
対佐藤戦の提案になります
of the Ajin Control Commission's
plan for countering Sato.
Are there any questions?
何か ご不明な点はございますか？
Yes... Ah...
（指揮官）
はい！
あの… この放水装置というのは？
What is this water spraying
equipment for?
IBM countermeasures.
（戸崎）
ＩＢＭ対策です
The latest research has shown
that IBMs are vulnerable to water.
最新の研究で―
ＩＢＭは 水に対して ぜい弱性が
あることが分かっていますので
（指揮官）
ああ…
What's the situation
with Grant Pharmaceuticals' security?
（戸崎）
グラント製薬の
警備状況はいかがですか？
（指揮官）
抜かりはありません
We've covered everything.
Since the day of the threat...
犯行予告の出された日から―
外部業者などの立ち入りも
厳しく制限していますし
...the entry of non-employees like vendors
has been strictly regulated.
And the bomb squad ran a screen throughout
the building that came up clear.
爆弾処理班による―
社内のスクリーニング検査も
クリアしました
We've also prepared
for aerial terrorist attacks.
航空機テロに関しても
厳戒警備態勢で臨んでいます
I see. However, our enemy is Sato.
なるほど
しかし 相手は佐藤です
Be sure not to let your guard down.
くれぐれも油断されぬように
（指揮官）
はあ
May I ask one last thing?
あの…
最後に１つよろしいですか？
What is it?
（戸崎）
何でしょう？
To capture the target,
are we really going to...
対象者の
捕獲方法についてなんですが
あの… 本当に
このような方法を取るのですか？
take these measures?
Is there a problem?
何か問題でも？
（指揮官）
はい あの…
Well...
I'm sorry to say this,
but aren't these inhumane?
こう言ってはなんですが
さすがに非人道的に過ぎるのではと
Ajins aren't human.
亜人は人間ではありません
So, the word "inhumane" doesn't apply.
ですから 非人道的という言葉も
当てはまらない
I see.
そう… ですか…
Well, then, I wish you luck.
では 健闘を祈ります
Takahashi, that's upside-down.
高橋君　それ 上下が逆だよ
I know.
（高橋）
わーってるよ
Oh, Gen, leave a 20 centimeter gap there.
あっ ゲン君 そこは
あと20センチ 間隔 空けて
Got it.
了解
（攻）
ふっ… ふっ… ふっ…
（扉の開く音）
（攻）あっ？
うわっ！　ああ…
Watch it!
危ねぇなっ！
（圭）
お前が欲しいって言ったんだろ？
You're the one who wanted that stuff.
（攻）
ああっ！？
ああ？
- See you.
- Hey, wait, Nagai!
（圭）
じゃあな
あ… おい 待て 永井！
Are you really not going to do anything?
It's just two days from now!
お前 ホントに何もしないのか？
もう 明後日だぞ！
We've already discussed that.
（圭）
その話は 前に済んだだろ
You and I might be able to stop Sato!
俺たちなら
止められるかもしんねぇんだぞ！
おいっ…
Hey!
（蹴る音）
（攻）くそっ…
Damn it!
（扉が開く音）
あっ
How would we do that?
どうやって止める？
- We'd fight him, of course!
- Seriously?
決まってんだろ！　戦うんだよ！
（圭）
はあ？
- I was stupid for asking.
- Hey, wait!
聞いた僕が馬鹿だったよ
（攻）
待て！
I know where Sato's hideout is!
We could report it to the police!
（攻）
俺は佐藤の隠れ家を知ってる！
警察に通報するってのは どうだ？
フッ いつまでも同じ場所に
いるわけないだろ
There's no way he'd stay
in the same place forever.
He's long since moved by now.
とっくに移動してるよ
After all, he let an idiot
like you escape.
お前っていう馬鹿を
逃がしてもいるわけだしな
Listen, Nagai. When I met Sato...
聞いてくれ 永井
佐藤に会った時 あいつは
“大量虐殺する”って言ってた
He said it would be a "massacre."
Even if the police try to stop him,
たとえ 警察の妨害があっても
亜人なら無差別に人殺しが出来る
an Ajin would still be able
to kill so many people.
Sato seriously plans
to go through with it.
佐藤は
ホントに本気でやるつもりだぞ
I'm sure he does.
（圭）
だろうね
でも 亜人だから危険なことが
出来るっていうなら―
But if he can do such dangerous things
'cause he's an Ajin,
俺たちだって そうだろ？
then so can we, right?
We might be able to stop him.
俺たちなら あいつを
止められるかもしれないんだぞ！
That's ridiculous.
話にならないね
I'm certain he's had high level
combat training.
あの人は まず間違いなく
高度な戦闘訓練を受けてる
Fighting him would be useless.
We'd have no chance.
戦うだけ無駄だよ　勝ち目はない
Then why were you practicing
with that black monster?
じゃあ なんで あの黒い
バケモンの練習してたんだよ？
Weren't you planning to use it
to fight back?
あれで戦うつもりだったんじゃ
ないのか！？
That's just my curiosity.
あれは ただの好奇心だよ
それに―
I need to know what I'm capable of
and what I'm not.
自分に何が出来て何が出来ないかを
把握しておくことは―
It has nothing to do with fighting.
戦いとは関係なく必要だしね
You really have no plans to fight him?
お前 ホントに戦う気はないのか？
I like my life right now.
今の暮らしは
結構 気に入ってるんだ
It's quiet and peaceful.
静かで平和で穏やかな生活だよ
I don't plan on throwing that away.
（圭）
それを捨てる気はないね
（攻）
くっ…
So as long as you're okay,
nothing else matters?
自分さえよけりゃ
それでいいのかよ
There's no one who doesn't think that.
そうじゃないやつなんて
いないだろ
くっ…
You're trash.
クズが！
You're an idiot.
馬鹿が
Keep your head down, and in those books!
（テレビ音声）
勉強中はもちろん
ランタンとしても大活躍の―
Great for studying,
and can even be used as a lantern.
マルチ電気スタンド
“ことなかれ君”！
The Appeaser, a new multi-light LED.
Buy now and get a free good-luck bracelet!
今なら
開運ブレスレットをセットに！
Why don't you make your room,
and your future, brighter?
お部屋も運気も
明るくしてみませんか？
お支払いは…
- I'm home.
- Oh, welcome back.
（圭）
ただいま
あ お帰り
（においをかぐ音）
あっ カレー？
Curry?
Ground beef curry,
just like you asked for.
注文どおり ひき肉カレーだよ
（圭）
わあ うれしいなぁ
- Yay, awesome!
- Oh, that's right.
（山中）
ああ そうだ
Here. You asked for this, too.
はい　これも注文どおり
You bought it for me...
買ってきてくれたんだ？
I had some errands in town, so I just
picked it up since I was there anyway.
（山中）
ちょうど 町に用があったからね
ついでだよ ついで
Thank you.
ありがとう
I'm sorry. It must have cost a lot.
ごめんね 散財させちゃって
Now, now, it won't do for you
to worry about money.
駄目だよ
金のことなんて気にしちゃ
A man should just be ready to deal
with whatever life throws at him.
男は どんと構えてりゃいいの
どーんとね
ハハハ 覚えときます
I'll remember that.
Are you going to contact someone?
（山中）
誰かと連絡取るのかい？
え？
I'm not sure it's a good idea
for you to be leaving so soon.
まだ まずいんじゃないのかい？
今 出てったら…
Oh, no. That's not it.
やだなぁ　違うよ
I just want to look something up.
ちょっと 調べたいことがあってね
はあ…
Oh, if that's all, you could
have looked it up at the library.
なんだい
調べ物なら図書館ですりゃいいのに
Kids these days
don't know what's good for them.
駄目だね 最近の若い子は
Machines won't tell you everything,
you know.
そんな機械は
何にも教えちゃくんないよ
ハハッ
CONSULTATION OVER THE PHONE OR EMAIL.
FREE IN CASE WE CAN'T RESOLVE.
- All finished?
- All finished.
無事 終わったかい？
ハハッ ばっちりっす
Looks like it went smoothly.
（佐藤）
はぁ… うまくいったようだ
- All right, let's go, Tanaka.
- Right.
じゃ 行こうか 田中君
（田中）
はい
（佐藤）
フッ フフフ…
You sure seem to be having fun.
（田中）
随分 楽しそうっすね
Whenever I play a video game,
私はね 田中君
ゲームをやる時は いつも
ハード･モードでプレーするんだ
I always play on hard mode.
はあ…　何すか 急に
What's this, all of a sudden?
The higher the difficulty...
難易度は…
...the more fun the game is.
（佐藤）
高ければ高いほど
面白いってことだよ
Sir. The Metropolitan Police Department
strongly urges you
社長　やはり
社員を帰宅させるべきです
to let your employees go home.
これは警視庁からの強い要請です
You should follow our advice.
Time is money.
（社長）
“時は金なり”だ
One day off would mean millions in losses.
１日の休業で
何億の損失になると思う？
- There are lives at stake.
- Money and human life are the same thing.
人命に関わります
（社長）
金と命は同義語だよ
And even if these IBM things
really do exist...
もし仮にＩＢＭなんてものが
実在するとして―
...what exactly do you think they can do?
何が出来るというんだ
I don't know how he plans to attack,
どう襲撃するつもりか知らんが―
but it's not possible
to get through this security.
この警備の中で
何かをやるなんて不可能だよ
（無線の音）
Copy that. Start it.
（機動隊員）
了解
始めろ
We don't have time to entertain the
so-called claims of the man in the hat.
（社長）
帽子の男のたわ言になど
付き合ってる時間はない
（奥山）
大丈夫だね
It should be fine.
Do you have an appointment?
（受付）ご予約のお客様で…
（銃声）
（守衛）お前！　何やってる？
You! What are you doing?
Your hands are shaking.
手 震えてんじゃん
- Yeah. Damn.
- Huh?
（高橋）
ああ やばい…
え？
This is crazy, man.
これは やばいぜ
All clear here.
異常なし
（銃声）
フフフフ…
（時報）
フッ
（爆発音）
（社長）はっ！
（どよめき）
（ざわめき）
あ… ああ…
（爆発音）
（笑い声）
（衝撃音）
あっ ホントにやっちゃうんだ？
He really did it.
あっ…
That was a blast.
スリル満点
（曽我部）
こ… こんな…
This...
Mr. Tosaki...
戸崎さん…
We're broadcasting
from above Grant Pharmaceuticals,
（モニター音声:キャスター）
こちら 犯行予告のあった
グラント製薬上空からの中継です
the target of recent threats.
（攻）
はぁっ… はぁっ…
I can't believe this! The building!
（テレビ音声:キャスター）
信じられません！　ビルです！
A high-rise building has collapsed
onto Grant Pharmaceuticals...
高層ビルが倒壊し…
くっそー…
（テレビ音声:キャスター）
押し… 押し潰したようです！
...which seems like it's been crushed!
So, he'd really go this far.
ここまでやるんだ？
Thanks, Okuyama.
（佐藤）
ありがとう 奥山君
Now.
さて
The enemy's not likely
to let me escape easily.
敵も
容易に逃がしてはくれないだろう
（若井(わかい)）
くっ　いつまで出し惜しみする気だ
コウマ陸佐！
How long are you planning
to hold back, Colonel Koma?
Why don't you mobilize the Anti-Ajins?
“対亜”を招集したらどうなんだ！
I can't.
That unit shouldn't even legally exist.
（コウマ）
駄目だ
あれは存在自体が違法の部隊
I can't send them out
in such a public place.
こんな公の場では出動させられん
I've been warned by my superiors.
上からも釘を刺されている
くっ… ぐっ…　完敗だな 戸崎
The battle's been lost, Tosaki!
The battle's just starting.
ここからですよ
（騒ぎ声）
There are more wounded over here!
（機動隊員）
こっちにもケガ人がいるぞ！
（指揮官）
あっ！
ああっ…
（太居(ふとい)）
さ… 佐藤だ！
It's Sato!
He's playing with us.
ふざけたやつだ
Now everyone.
さあ みんな
You don't actually think
we've won with that, do you?
これくらいで
勝ったなどと思ってないな？
What's the strongest armed force
in this country?
この国最強の部隊とは？
The Self-Defense Force?
自衛隊か？
No. With no actual battle experience,
they're not even in the running.
違う
一度も実戦経験のないやつらなど
論外甚だしい
And so...
となると…
That's right...
（佐藤）
そう
The Metropolitan Police
Special Assault Team.
警視庁特殊急襲部隊
An elite team with real combat experience,
テロや凶悪事件発生時
交渉より制圧を優先し展開する―
developed to focus
on tactical supremacy...
...for incidents that involve terrorism
or extreme violence.
（戸崎）
実動経験のある精鋭部隊だ
Therefore it follows
that if we beat them...
極論 彼らに勝てれば―
...then we are the strongest armed force
in the country.
私たちは
この国最強の軍隊と言える
I ask the public to decide
based on this battle...
国民に問う　この戦闘で判断せよ
（タブレット端末音声:佐藤）
我々と人間 どちら側につくべきか
...whose side they should be on:
ours or the humans'.
Mr. Tosaki, the Hat's live broadcasting
from his point of view.
（曽我部）
戸崎先輩
帽子は自分の視野を
ライブ配信してます
All of Japan will be watching this battle!
日本中が この戦闘を見る！
負けるわけにはいきませんよ！
We can't afford to lose.
The same is true for him.
やつも同じだ
さあ…
Now then...
It's show time.
ショウタイムだ
TO BE CONTINUED
If my wish would come true
願い叶(かな)うなら
もう一度
Once again
I wanna touch your heart
君の心に
触れていたい
No matter how dark it gets
どんな闇でも
探してるんだ
I'll be searching
For my one
たったひとつの
光を
And only light
As I look up to the stars
Even though you are far
遠いけど
同じ星空　見上げてる
You're looking up at the same starry sky
In the sky of my heart
心の空には
雫(こぼ)れ落ちそうな
It's about to spill over
Your smile and
君の笑顔と
ぬくもり
Your warmth
Hear me
Until I went away and
Faced the lonely days
愛することの意味なんて
I thought I could understand
What it means to love
分かってたつもりだった
Feeling everything that
Was right in front of me
大切なもの失って
Losing something precious
本当の愛に気付いて
Realizing real love
I'll tell you now
I'll tell you now,
Just how close you are